Noorhan Sharawy

Phone:+201015734776

Email:noorhan756@gmail.com

Address: Cairo, Egypt

Customer Service Representative

I aspire to join a collaborative work environment where my strong communication skills and team-oriented mindset can help drive collective achievements. Passionate about driving success in the enterprise industry and professional marketing of fast-moving goods. Having worked for more than three years in national companies, I have also been able to skillfully deal with clients and sell banking products for more than 4 years. I have gained experience in different fields, including digital marketing and communications services. Social and sales. • A goal-oriented sales manager with years of sales experience. I have excellent sales, negotiation and closing skills. Known for great presentations and skill in growing audiences to improve sales. Self-motivated outside sales professional with experience in both technical, non-technical and fast-paced team environments. An expert in building relationships and dealing with audiences at all levels and different communities..

Personal Info

Gender : Female DOB : 14.01.1996

Nationality: Egyptian

Experience

Customer Service

Vodafone Egypt

• Handling customer,Responding to customers and following up with them to find out these problems regarding customer satisfaction and company policy.

Call Center

Aug 2019 - Oct 2020

Oct 2018 - Jul 2019

We Egypt

• Streamlined call center operations, optimizing staff scheduling and reducing average call wait times. Improved caller satisfaction by implementing effective coaching and training techniques for call center staff.

Accountant

Aug 2020 - Mar 2021

Al AML Company

• Enhanced financial decision-making capabilities by providing timely, accurate information to management through regular performance reports. Trained new employees on accounting principles and company procedures. Reviewed accounts, resolved coding areas, and tracked recurring expenses for accrual entry. Established strong relationships with banking partners to facilitate access to various financial services and secure favorable lending terms for the organization.

Education

Mansoura University

Oct 2013 - Jul 2018

Bachelor's degree in Media and Mass Communication

· Digital Media And Mass Communication. · journalist · presentation · Tv program · voice over · media app · mass communication · public Relations

Senior Sales Executive

Apr 2021 – CONTINUE

National Bank Of Egypt

· I support the direct sales team with administrative tasks to help sales representatives close deals. Selling the product or service to new and old customers. Facilitate regular team meetings focused on goal setting, progress updates, and strategy refinement for continuous improvement efforts. Exceed sales goals by implementing strong sales programs. Develop and maintain strong working relationships with professionals. Manage digital marketing initiatives according to consumer goals and needs. Passionate about learning and committed to continuous improvement. Show respect, friendliness, and willingness to help where needed. Develop relationships with prominent clients by successfully using qualitative selling techniques. Built diverse and consistent sales portfolio. Established longlasting relationships with key clients through effective account management and consistent communication. Met existing customers to review current services and expand sales opportunities. Trained new employees on customer service, money handling and organizing strategies.

Suze University

Sept 2020 – Jul 2021

Diploma In Arabic Language

• Education of Individuals in Secondary Special Education Programs. • Vocational training to work in schools. • Completed professional development in Arabic. Continuing education in Arabic.

Achievement

Leading and training a number of new employees

I Obtained the Professional Seller Certificate from the National Bank of Egypt

I obtained an ideal student certificate from Mansoura University

International Computer Driving Licence (IC3)

 $\cdot \cdot \cdot \text{Outlook} \cdot \text{Digital Transformation} \cdot \text{Microsoft office} \cdot \text{word} \cdot \text{Excel} \cdot \text{Access} \cdot \text{Mail} \cdot \text{PowerPoint}$

International Computer Driving Licence (ICDL)

Presentation Course

Voice Over Course

Skills	Marketing
	MS Office
	Management
	Interpersonal communication
	Planning and coordination
	Problem solving
	Creativity
	Customer Service
	Active listening
	Data analysis
Language	Arabic
	English

Interests

Reading

Photography

Travel

Writing

Public speaking